Guide to the Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project Records, 1964-2010
  - Texas Christian University, Moudy Visual Arts & Communications Building, 1981
    - Specifications (Box 294)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 294–295)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 256)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 296, Box 298–299)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 296, Box 298–299)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 296–299)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 299)
  - Union Carbide Corporation World Headquarters, 1982
    Job number: 7605
    Job location: Danbury, CT
    - Correspondence (Box 424–428, Box 430, Box 464, Box 487–488)
    - Contracts (Box 429)
    - Specifications (Box 426, Box 429–430)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 424–425)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 110)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 428, Box 428–429)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 433–435, Box 438–447, Box 449–450, Box 452–459)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 431–433, Box 436–438, Box 447–451)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 435–438, Box 449)
  - Exxon Chemical Company Headquarters
    Job number: 7701
    Job location: Fairfield, CT
    - Correspondence (Box 213)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 213)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 212)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 216–217)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 214–215)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 214–215)
  - General Foods Corporation Headquarters, 1983
    Job number: 7704
    Job location: Ryebrook, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 518–521, Box 526, Box 528–529, Box 564, Box 577)
    - Specifications (Box 520, Box 522–524, Box 527, Box 529–533)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 518, Box 520)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 125)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 525, Box 544, Box 546–547, Box 553–559)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 546–547, Box 553–559)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 544–545, Box 548–552, Box 554)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 550)
  - US Embassy London
    Job number: 7707
    Job location: London, England
    - Correspondence (Box 489)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 489)
  - Cummins Engine Company Corporate Headquarters, 1984
    Job number: 7709
    - Correspondence (Box 373–381, Box 412, Box 464, Box 560)
    - Contracts (Box 373)
    - Specifications (Box 376)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 373, Box 380)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 258)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 403, Box 407–410)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 401–402, Box 405–410)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 401–402)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 402, Box 404, Box 406)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Expansion, 1962; 1966
    Job number: 7708
    Job location: Holmdel, NJ
    - Correspondence (Box 581–584)
    - Specifications (Box 582–584)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 584)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 585–586, Box 592)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 585–592)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 585–592)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 585, Box 587–588, Box 591)
  - John Deere Financial Services Headquarters, 1981
    Job number: 7803
    - Correspondence (Box 327, Box 343, Box 463)
    - Specifications (Box 327, Box 343)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 327)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 342)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 340)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 340, Box 346–347)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 338–339)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 339)
  - Jefferson National Expansion Memorial
    Job number: 79--
    Job location: St. Louis, MO
    - Correspondence (Box 489)
  - New York Historical Society
    - Correspondence (Box 489)
  - Miller, J. Irwin and Xenia S. Residence, 1981
    Job number: 7903
    Job location: Hobe Sound, FL
    Project type: Residential
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 370–371)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 370–371)
  - Conoco Inc. Petroleum Headquarters, 1986
    Job number: 7904
    Job location: Houston, TX
    - Correspondence (Box 317–324, Box 344, Box 460, Box 464, Box 466, Box 489)
    - Specifications (Box 317, Box 319)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 317)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 259)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 308–309, Box 315–316, Box 319, Box 348–355)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 304–310, Box 316, Box 348–355)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 301–303, Box 311–315)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 301, Box 311–312, Box 315)
  - John Deere Educational Center
    Job number: 7908
    - Correspondence (Box 326, Box 463)
    - Specifications (Box 326, Box 343)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 326)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 326)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 356–360)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 360–361)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 361–362)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 361)
  - Central Park Zoo, 1988
    Job number: 8001
    Project type: Zoo
    - Correspondence (Box 468–472)
    - Specifications (Box 472, Box 516–517, Box 577)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 468, Box 471)
    - Slides (Box 471)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 251)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 486)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 486)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 473–480, Box 517A)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 481–486)
  - 51 West 52nd Street - EF Hutton, 1987
    Job number: 8004
    - Correspondence (Box 500–501)
    - Specifications (Box 500–501)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 499)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 497–498)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 510–515)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 502–509, Box 596–598)
  - John Deere Computer Center
    Job number: 8101
    Project type: Not Built
    - Correspondence (Box 327)
    - Specifications (Box 327)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 327)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 345)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 341)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 341)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 341)
  - Denver Block I Development
    Job number: 8105
    - Correspondence (Box 489)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 610)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 610)
  - General Foods Corporation - North Street Renovation, 1985
    Job number: 8205
    Job location: White Plains, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 561–564, Box 577, Box 593–595)
    - Specifications (Box 561–564, Box 594–595)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 565, Box 568, Box 574–576)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 565, Box 568–576)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 566–568)
  - Bouygues World Headquarters, 1988
    Job number: 8302
    Job location: Paris, France
    - Correspondence (Box 156–158, Box 463, Box 465)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 156, Box 463)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 124)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 164–167)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 159–163)
  - Marriott Corporation Corporate Headquarters Complex
    Job number: 8711
    Job location: Virginia
    - Correspondence (Box 609, Box 611)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 609, Box 611)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 614)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 612–614)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 614)
  - 1000 Westchester Avenue, Schulman Realty Group
    Job number: 8801
    Job location: Harrison, NY
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 617)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 618–619)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 618–619)
  - Millenia Singapore Office Buildings & Hotel, 1998
    Job number: 9007
    Job location: Singapore
    Project type: Office/Retail/Hotel
    - Scrapbooks (Box 260)
  - Cummins/Tata Cummins Private Limited
    Job number: 9402
    Job location: Jamshedpur, India
    - Correspondence (Box 416, Box 492)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 416, Box 492)
  - Cummins Engine Company, Columbus Engine Plant, 1998
    Job number: 9403
    - Correspondence (Box 413–415)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 423)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 417–423)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 423)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 417)
  - Cummins / Fleetguard Filter Company Ltd, 1997
    Job number: 9408
    Job location: Shanghai, China
    - Correspondence (Box 390–391)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 390)
  - Cummins Electronics
    Job number: 9414
    - Correspondence (Box 416)
  - Cummins Newage Assembly Plant, 1997
    Job number: 9613
    Job location: Wuxi, China
    - Correspondence (Box 416)
  - United States Patent and Trademark Office
    Job number: 9617
    Job location: Alexandria, VI
    - Correspondence (Box 615)
    - Specifications (Box 615)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 616)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 616)
  - Cummins Engine Company, Bejing Offices
    Job number: 9705
    Job location: Bejing, China
    - Correspondence (Box 416)
  - Banco Santander Central Hispano "Ciudad Grupo Santander", 2005
    Job number: 9911
    Job location: Madrid, Spain
    - Scrapbooks (Box 250)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1971
    Job number: 6704
    - Scrapbooks (Box 225–226)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, American Wing with the Charles Engelhard Court, 1980
    Job number: 6704x15
    - Scrapbooks (Box 227)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Robert Lehman Wing, 1975
    Job number: 6704x01
    - Scrapbooks (Box 228)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Temple of Dendur in the Sackler Wing, 1978
    Job number: 6704x03
    - Scrapbooks (Box 229)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Egyptian Wing, Phase I, II and III, 1982
    Job number: 6704x09 6704x39
    - Scrapbooks (Box 230)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Michael C. Rockefeller Wing for the Arts of Africa, Oceania and the Americas, 1982
    Job number: 6704x10
    - Scrapbooks (Box 231)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Andre Meyer Galleries, 1980
    Job number: 6704x55
    - Scrapbooks (Box 232)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Astor Court, 1980
    Job number: 7705
    - Scrapbooks (Box 233)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Lila Acheson Wallace Wing for 20th Century Art (Southwest Wing), 1987
    Job number: 8002
    - Scrapbooks (Box 234)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New Japanese Galleries, 1987
    Job number: 8402
    - Scrapbooks (Box 235)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, European Sculpture and Decorative Arts Wing & the Carroll & Milton Petrie European Sculpt Ct, 1988
    Job number: 8502
    - Scrapbooks (Box 236)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Later Chinese Galleries, 1993
    Job number: 9301
    - Scrapbooks (Box 237)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Greek and Roman Courtyard, Greek and Roman, Greek & Roman Wing Phase IV, 2008
    Job number: 9206 9313 0016
    - Scrapbooks (Box 238)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, The Ruth and Harold D. Uris Center for Education, Phase I and II, 2007
    Job number: 15
    - Scrapbooks (Box 239)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Law School, 1983-1987
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 191)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 191)
- Additional Material, 1981-1984; Accession 2012-M-042
  The addition consists of interviews conducted by Susan O'Keefe with Kevin Roche and others, notes and bibliographic index cards.
  - Susan O'Keefe interviews with Kevin Roche
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Interview 1 & 2, 1983 September 6-1983 October 7; 1 (Box 1)
    - Interview 3, 1983 November 15; 1 (Box 2)
    - Interview 4, 1984 January 13; 1 (Box 3)
    - Interview 5, 1984 February 17; 1 (Box 4)
    - Interview 6, 1984 March 30; 1 (Box 4)
      - Use Copy, Undated; 2 (Box 4Ua–4Ub)
    - Interview 7 & 8, 1984 August 1-1984 August 24; 1 (Box 5)
    - Interview 9, 1984 December 20; 1 (Box 6)
  - Interviews of Others
    - Brady, Alfred, 1984 May 4; 2 (Box 7–8)
    - Brioscú, Aodhagán, 1984 May 7-1984 May 8; 3 (Box 9–11)
    - Cantwell, Wilfrid, 1984 May 3; 2 (Box 12–13)
    - Fox, Kevin, 1984 May 4; 1 (Box 14)
      General
      Includes commentary on Side A.
    - General Foods, Undated; 1 (Box 15)
    - Hayer, William (Mitchelstown), Undated; 1 (Box 16)
      See also: Box 27 Riordan, Patrick
    - Herrera, Alex (LPC), No Year, January 23; 1 (Box 17)
    - Kiersay, Kenneth, 1984 May 12; 1 (Box 18)
    - McDermott, Matthew, and Cathal O'Neill, 1984 May 2; 1 (Box 19)
    - Minkin, Irving, 1981 November 20; 1 (Box 20)
    - Mumford, Louis, Undated; 1 (Box 21)
    - O'Connell, Arthur, 1984 May 9; 1 (Box 22)
    - O'Keeffe, John (Boston St. School), 1984 May 2; 1 (Box 23)
    - O'Neill, Cathal
      See: McDermott, Matthew
    - Roche, Pierce, 1984 May 13; 2 (Box 24–25)
    - Rothery, Sean, 1984 May 4; 1 (Box 26)
    - Riordan, Patrick, and William Hayer (Mitchelstown), Undated; 1 (Box 27)
    - Scott, Michael, 1984 May 3; 1 (Box 28)
    - Scott, Patrick, 1984 May 2; 1 (Box 29)
    - Walker, Robin and Dorothy, 1984 May 1; 3 (Box 30–32)
  - Interview Notes, Undated; 2 (Box 33–34)
  - Roche, Kevin Interview on Irish Television, 1983 November; 1 (Box 35)
  - Unidentified, Undated; 2 (Box 36–37)
  - Bibliographic Index Cards, Undated (Box 38)